how to pay manual lifee insurance online
banking Manulife bank is a Canadian
online bank offering savings accounts
mortgages and other financial services
without traditional branches customers
access their accounts through online
banking mobile apps and
ATMs first download manual life Bank
application from Google Play store or
App Store then log into your account
with username and password on homepage
tap on the menu tap on payment then tap
make a payment choose the policy you
want to pay and tap pay premium tap the
editable field and enter total amount
you intend to pay scroll down and tap
the relationship of credit card holder
to insured then take the terms and
conditions check box before tapping
continue to payment enter your card
details and click on the submit
button that's it thanks for watching